[
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Baseball", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Basketball", 
      "Football", 
      "Ice Hockey"
    ], 
    "question": "Which sport is played by the Minnesota Twins?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Miami", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Dallas", 
      "Los Angeles", 
      "Atlanta"
    ], 
    "question": "In American Football, where is the Orange Bowl?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Croquet", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tennis", 
      "Badminton", 
      "Billiards"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Game Makes Use Of Hoops", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Two", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Five", 
      "Four", 
      "Three"
    ], 
    "question": "In a game of netball how many players on a team are allowed To score?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "John McEnroe", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Pete Sampras", 
      "Bjorn Borg", 
      "Ivan Lendl"
    ], 
    "question": "Which tennis player was famous for the 'You cannot be serious'' outburst?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Celtics", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Bruins", 
      "Marlins", 
      "Bellringers"
    ], 
    "question": "Basketball: The Boston ___________.", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Andy Cole", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Wayne Rooney", 
      "Sergio Aguero"
    ], 
    "question": "Alan Shearer was the first player to score 200 Premiership goals. Who was the second?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Baby Pac-Man", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Miss Pac-Man", 
      "Mrs Pac-Man", 
      "Super Pac-Man"
    ], 
    "question": "What was the hybrid pinball/video game in the Pac-Man series?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Uruguay", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Brazil", 
      "West Germany", 
      "France"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Country Won The First Football World Cup? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Mayfair", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Kensington", 
      "Trafalgar Square", 
      "Old Kent Road"
    ], 
    "question": "What Is The Most Valuble Property In A Game Of British Monopoly?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "3,000 Metres", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "10,000 Metres", 
      "5,000 Metres", 
      "8,000 Metres"
    ], 
    "question": "Over What Distance Is A Steeple Chase Run?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Ipswich Town", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Plymouth Argyle", 
      "Norwich City", 
      "Bristol Rovers"
    ], 
    "question": "Which English football team are nicknamed the Tractor Boys?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Houston", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Atlanta", 
      "Settle", 
      "Miami"
    ], 
    "question": "The Rockets Basketball Team & The Astros Baseball Team Both Hail From Which US City?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "5", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "1", 
      "0", 
      "3"
    ], 
    "question": "How Many Dice Do You Have In A Backgammon Set?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Cricket", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Rugby", 
      "Tennis", 
      "Bowling"
    ], 
    "question": "The Duckworth Lewis Method Is Used To Keep The Score In Which Sport?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Inky, Pinky, Blinky & Clyde", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Inky, Pinky, Blinky & Floyd", 
      "Dinky, Pinky, Winky & Clyde", 
      "Dinky, Pinky, Blinky & Floyd"
    ], 
    "question": "What Are The Names Of The Ghosts In The Classic 80's Video Game Pac Man? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Mrs White, Miss Scarlet, Mrs Peacock", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Mrs Plum, Miss Jade, Mrs Scarlett", 
      "Mrs White, Miss Gold, Mrs Green", 
      "Miss Silver, Mrs Pink, Mrs Indigo"
    ], 
    "question": "Name The 3 Female Characters In The Game Cluedo", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Greece", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Argentina", 
      "Japan", 
      "Australia", 
      "Russia"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Country Hosted The 2004 Summer Olympics?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Four", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Six", 
      "Three", 
      "Five"
    ], 
    "question": "How many human players are in a polo team?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Steffi Graff", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Billie Jean King", 
      "Venus Williams", 
      "Maria Sharapova"
    ], 
    "question": "Which player won her last tennis Grand Slam Tournament in Paris in 1999?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Formula One", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Rugby", 
      "Cricket", 
      "Tennis"
    ], 
    "question": "Monza & Silverstone Are Venues For Which Sport?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Surfing", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Skate Boarding", 
      "Skiing", 
      "Boxing"
    ], 
    "question": "What sport do the following terms belong to - \"Hotdog & Bottom Trun\"?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Andy Cole", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Wayne Rooney", 
      "Sergio Aguero"
    ], 
    "question": "Alan Shearer was the first player to score 200 Premiership goals. Who was the second?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Four", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Six", 
      "Three", 
      "Five"
    ], 
    "question": "How many seams are there on a football (American)?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Eric Bristow", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Gerwyn Price", 
      "Gary Anderson", 
      "Phil Taylor"
    ], 
    "question": "Which darts player became the first in his sport to receive an MBE in 1989?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Cricket", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Rugby", 
      "Tennis", 
      "Bowling"
    ], 
    "question": "The Duckworth Lewis Method Is Used To Keep The Score In Which Sport?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Middlesex", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Essex", 
      "Surrey", 
      "Berkshire"
    ], 
    "question": "In Which County Is Lord's Cricket Ground?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "A Pineapple", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "A Strawberry", 
      "An Apple", 
      "A Raspberry"
    ], 
    "question": "What Type Of Fruit Is Depicted On Top Of The Men's Singles Trophy At Wimbledon?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Catcher", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Pitcher", 
      "Guard", 
      "Steer"
    ], 
    "question": "What Is The Name Of The Player In Baseball Who Is Positioned Behind The Home Plate", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "5", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "1", 
      "0", 
      "3"
    ], 
    "question": "How Many Dice Do You Have In A Backgammon Set?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Baseball", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Basketball", 
      "Football", 
      "Ice Hockey"
    ], 
    "question": "Which sport is played by the Minnesota Twins?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Black", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "White", 
      "Red", 
      "Brown"
    ], 
    "question": "What Colour Is The 8 Ball In A Game Of Pool?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Andy Cole", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Wayne Rooney", 
      "Sergio Aguero"
    ], 
    "question": "Alan Shearer was the first player to score 200 Premiership goals. Who was the second?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Andre Agassi", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Roger Federer", 
      "Pete Sampras", 
      "Andy Roddick"
    ], 
    "question": "In April 2003 Who Became The Oldest Man To Be Rated No1 In The World Tennis Association Rankings At The Age Of 33?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Hill", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Schumacher", 
      "Hunt", 
      "Villeneuve"
    ], 
    "question": "What Surname Has Been Shared By Three Formula One Champions Of The 20th Century?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Ryder Cup", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The FIFA World Cup", 
      "The UEFA Champion's League", 
      "The America's Cup"
    ], 
    "question": "The Solheim Cup Is The Woman's Equivalent Of Which Famous Sporting Cup?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Five", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Twelve", 
      "Two", 
      "Nine"
    ], 
    "question": "How Many Consecutive Wimbledon Titles Did Bjorn Borg Win?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Golf", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tennis", 
      "Boxing", 
      "Rugby"
    ], 
    "question": "With Which Sport Would You Associate Colin Montgomerie?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Let", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Dus", 
      "Par", 
      "See"
    ], 
    "question": "What 3 Letter Word It The Name Given To A Replayed Point In Tennis?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "5", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "1", 
      "0", 
      "3"
    ], 
    "question": "How Many Dice Do You Have In A Backgammon Set?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Silverstone", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Brands Hatch", 
      "Thruxton", 
      "Knockhill"
    ], 
    "question": "At Which Course Is The British Grand Prix Held?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Ryder Cup", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The FIFA World Cup", 
      "The UEFA Champion's League", 
      "The America's Cup"
    ], 
    "question": "The Solheim Cup Is The Woman's Equivalent Of Which Famous Sporting Cup?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "American Football", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Soccer", 
      "Baseball", 
      "Basketball"
    ], 
    "question": "What sport do the following terms belong to - \"Tight End & Wide Receiver\"?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "John McEnroe", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Pete Sampras", 
      "Bjorn Borg", 
      "Ivan Lendl"
    ], 
    "question": "Which tennis player was famous for the 'You cannot be serious'' outburst?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Broncos", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Redskins", 
      "Steelers", 
      "Colts"
    ], 
    "question": "The Denver ____?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Nurburgring", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Hokkenheim", 
      "Spa", 
      "Monza"
    ], 
    "question": "Which German Grand Prix circuit was used for a Formula 1 race for the last time in 1976, when Niki Lauda was almost killed?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Viv Anderson", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Raheem Sterling", 
      "John Barnes", 
      "Paul Ince"
    ], 
    "question": "Which footballer was England's first black player?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Super heavyweight", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Flyweight", 
      "Heavyweight", 
      "Maxweight"
    ], 
    "question": "What is the heaviest class of weight-lifting?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Robotic Operating Buddy", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Random Object Builder", 
      "Realistic Orbital Belt", 
      "Routed Oval Beam"
    ], 
    "question": "What did the letters in ROB (the old NES peripheral) stand for?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Grouse", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Deer", 
      "Fox", 
      "Pheasant"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Shooting Season Begins On The Glorious Twelfth?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "16", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "12", 
      "10", 
      "14"
    ], 
    "question": "How many balls are on a pool table at the start of a game?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Golf", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tennis", 
      "Boxing", 
      "Rugby"
    ], 
    "question": "With Which Sport Would You Associate Colin Montgomerie?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "300", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "100", 
      "200", 
      "250"
    ], 
    "question": "In tenpin bowling, how many points does a perfect game consist of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Newcastle United", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Liverpool", 
      "Arsenal", 
      "Aston Villa"
    ], 
    "question": "In 1992 Kevin Keegan became manager of which football club?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Baseball", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Football", 
      "Basketball", 
      "Ice Hockey"
    ], 
    "question": "This sport is called the \"American pastime\"?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Greece", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Argentina", 
      "Japan", 
      "Australia", 
      "Russia"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Country Hosted The 2004 Summer Olympics?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Oliver McCall", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Mike Tyson", 
      "Frank Bruno", 
      "Alex Brush"
    ], 
    "question": "Who was the first boxer to defeat Lennox Lewis in a professional bout?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Everton", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Chelsea", 
      "Liverpool", 
      "Sunderland"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Football Team Are Known As The Toffees", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "John McEnroe", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Pete Sampras", 
      "Bjorn Borg", 
      "Ivan Lendl"
    ], 
    "question": "Which tennis player was famous for the 'You cannot be serious'' outburst?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Silverstone", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Brands Hatch", 
      "Thruxton", 
      "Knockhill"
    ], 
    "question": "At Which Course Is The British Grand Prix Held?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Mrs White, Miss Scarlet, Mrs Peacock", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Mrs Plum, Miss Jade, Mrs Scarlett", 
      "Mrs White, Miss Gold, Mrs Green", 
      "Miss Silver, Mrs Pink, Mrs Indigo"
    ], 
    "question": "Name The 3 Female Characters In The Game Cluedo", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Long Jump", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "High Jump", 
      "Triple Jump", 
      "Pole Vault"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Jump Event Did Carl Lewis Specialize In As Well As The Sprint?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Atalanta", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Detroit", 
      "Miami", 
      "Houston", 
      "Boston", 
      "Chicago", 
      "Denver"
    ], 
    "question": "In Baseball where do the braves come from?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "1970's", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "1960's", 
      "1950's", 
      "1940's"
    ], 
    "question": "In which decade was cricket's first World Cup Final played?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Super heavyweight", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Flyweight", 
      "Heavyweight", 
      "Maxweight"
    ], 
    "question": "What is the heaviest class of weight-lifting?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "16", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "12", 
      "10", 
      "14"
    ], 
    "question": "How many balls are on a pool table at the start of a game?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Barcelona", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Rome", 
      "London", 
      "Paris"
    ], 
    "question": "Where were the 1992 Olympics held?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "5", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "1", 
      "0", 
      "3"
    ], 
    "question": "How Many Dice Do You Have In A Backgammon Set?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Andy Cole", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Wayne Rooney", 
      "Sergio Aguero"
    ], 
    "question": "Alan Shearer was the first player to score 200 Premiership goals. Who was the second?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Shigeru Miyamoto", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Yu Suzuki", 
      "Satoru Iwata", 
      "Gunpei Yokoi"
    ], 
    "question": "Which legendary games designer/producer created the Super Mario Brothers franchise for Nintendo?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Nintendo Entertainment System", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Natural Emitting Screen", 
      "Near Energy Source"
    ], 
    "question": "What does the acronym \"NES\" stand for?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "A Driver Has Been Disqualified", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Race Has Been Won", 
      "A Driver Has Died", 
      "The Fastest Lap Has Been Set"
    ], 
    "question": "In Formula One what does it mean when they are waving a black flag?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Roll", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Dough", 
      "Pull", 
      "Wrap"
    ], 
    "question": "Who is Mega Man's sister?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Surfing", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Skate Boarding", 
      "Skiing", 
      "Boxing"
    ], 
    "question": "What sport do the following terms belong to - \"Hotdog & Bottom Trun\"?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Ronnie O'Sullivan", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Stephen Hendry", 
      "John Higgins", 
      "Steve Davis"
    ], 
    "question": "Which snooker player was fined 20,000 for assaulting an official in 1996?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Baby Pac-Man", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Miss Pac-Man", 
      "Mrs Pac-Man", 
      "Super Pac-Man"
    ], 
    "question": "What was the hybrid pinball/video game in the Pac-Man series?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Golf", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tennis", 
      "Boxing", 
      "Rugby"
    ], 
    "question": "With Which Sport Would You Associate Colin Montgomerie?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "5 And 1", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "1 and 19", 
      "7 and 13", 
      "15 and 5"
    ], 
    "question": "What Numbers Are Either Side Of 20 On A Dartboard", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Andre Agassi", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Roger Federer", 
      "Pete Sampras", 
      "Andy Roddick"
    ], 
    "question": "In April 2003 Who Became The Oldest Man To Be Rated No1 In The World Tennis Association Rankings At The Age Of 33?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Martina Hingis", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Serena Williams", 
      "Maria Sharapova", 
      "Steffi Graf"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Female Tennis Star Was Handed A Two Year Ban After Testing Positive For Cocaine At Wimbledon In 2007?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "An Ice Skating Rink", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "A Football Pitch", 
      "A Tennis Court", 
      "A Rugby Pitch"
    ], 
    "question": "In the world of sport what has the maximum dimensions of 60 metres by 30 metres?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Martina Hingis", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Serena Williams", 
      "Maria Sharapova", 
      "Steffi Graf"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Female Tennis Star Was Handed A Two Year Ban After Testing Positive For Cocaine At Wimbledon In 2007?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Celtics", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Bruins", 
      "Marlins", 
      "Bellringers"
    ], 
    "question": "Basketball: The Boston ___________.", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Four", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Six", 
      "Three", 
      "Five"
    ], 
    "question": "How many human players are in a polo team?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Let", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Dus", 
      "Par", 
      "See"
    ], 
    "question": "What 3 Letter Word It The Name Given To A Replayed Point In Tennis?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Golf", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tennis", 
      "Boxing", 
      "Rugby"
    ], 
    "question": "With Which Sport Would You Associate Colin Montgomerie?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Silverstone", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Brands Hatch", 
      "Thruxton", 
      "Knockhill"
    ], 
    "question": "At Which Course Is The British Grand Prix Held?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Hill", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Schumacher", 
      "Hunt", 
      "Villeneuve"
    ], 
    "question": "What Surname Has Been Shared By Three Formula One Champions Of The 20th Century?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Argentina", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South Africa", 
      "Uruguay", 
      "Brazil"
    ], 
    "question": "The Pumas Are The Rugby Team Of Which Country?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "4", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "6", 
      "11", 
      "2"
    ], 
    "question": "How Many Players Are In A Polo Team?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Silverstone", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Brands Hatch", 
      "Thruxton", 
      "Knockhill"
    ], 
    "question": "At Which Course Is The British Grand Prix Held?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Eric Bristow", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Gerwyn Price", 
      "Gary Anderson", 
      "Phil Taylor"
    ], 
    "question": "Which darts player became the first in his sport to receive an MBE in 1989?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "One", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Two", 
      "Three", 
      "Four"
    ], 
    "question": "How many referees work a soccer game?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Sailboat racing", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Baseball", 
      "Volleyball", 
      "Golf"
    ], 
    "question": "In which sport is the America's Cup awarded? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Calcutta Cup", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Davis Cup", 
      "Roobis Cup", 
      "Hadrian's Cup"
    ], 
    "question": "Name The Rugby Union Trophy For Which England & Scotland Compete", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Catcher", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Pitcher", 
      "Guard", 
      "Steer"
    ], 
    "question": "What Is The Name Of The Player In Baseball Who Is Positioned Behind The Home Plate", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "24", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "16", 
      "20", 
      "12"
    ], 
    "question": "How Many Draughts Are On The Board At The Start Of A Game?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Oxford", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Manchester", 
      "London", 
      "York", 
      "Southampton", 
      "Norwich"
    ], 
    "question": "In which English city did Roger Bannister become the first man to run a mile in under 4 minutes? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "110m Hurdles", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Pole Vault", 
      "Discus", 
      "Steeple Chase"
    ], 
    "question": "In Which Athletic Event Was Colin Jackson A Dominant Figure?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Basketball", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Volleyball", 
      "Football", 
      "Baseball"
    ], 
    "question": "What Sport Do The Harlem Globetrotters Play?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Swim Across The English Channel", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Fly Solo Across the Atlantic", 
      "Run a marathon in under 2.5 hours"
    ], 
    "question": "What in 1926, did Gertrude Ederle become the first woman to do?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Jack", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Nightmare", 
      "The Flush", 
      "The Drone"
    ], 
    "question": "What Is The Name Of The White Ball In A Game Of Bowls?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Six", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Four", 
      "Eight", 
      "Two"
    ], 
    "question": "How many pockets does a snooker table have?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "A glass eye", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "A deck of cards", 
      "Keys", 
      "A yo-yo"
    ], 
    "question": "With what did cricketer Mansoor Ali Khan Pataudi frequently play with in his hands?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Basketball", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Volleyball", 
      "Football", 
      "Baseball"
    ], 
    "question": "What Sport Do The Harlem Globetrotters Play?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Martina Navratilova", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steffi Graf", 
      "Chris Evert", 
      "Margaret Court", 
      "Billie Jean King"
    ], 
    "question": "Who was the 1978 Wimbledon Women's Singles champ?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Swim Across The English Channel", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Fly Solo Across the Atlantic", 
      "Run a marathon in under 2.5 hours"
    ], 
    "question": "What in 1926, did Gertrude Ederle become the first woman to do?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "George Foreman", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Joe Frazier", 
      "Wilfredo Gomez", 
      "Roberto Duran"
    ], 
    "question": "Who Did Muhammed Ali Fight In 'The Rumble In The Jungle''?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Baby Pac-Man", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Miss Pac-Man", 
      "Mrs Pac-Man", 
      "Super Pac-Man"
    ], 
    "question": "What was the hybrid pinball/video game in the Pac-Man series?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Argentina", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South Africa", 
      "Uruguay", 
      "Brazil"
    ], 
    "question": "The Pumas Are The Rugby Team Of Which Country?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Oche", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Div", 
      "The Par", 
      "The Sod"
    ], 
    "question": "What Is the Mark Behind Which Dart Player Must Stand Called?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Calcutta Cup", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Davis Cup", 
      "Roobis Cup", 
      "Hadrian's Cup"
    ], 
    "question": "Name The Rugby Union Trophy For Which England & Scotland Compete", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Black", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "White", 
      "Red", 
      "Brown"
    ], 
    "question": "What Colour Is The 8 Ball In A Game Of Pool?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Five", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Six", 
      "Seven", 
      "Eight"
    ], 
    "question": "How Many Players Are In A Basketball Team?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Croquet", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tennis", 
      "Badminton", 
      "Billiards"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Game Makes Use Of Hoops", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "A glass eye", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "A deck of cards", 
      "Keys", 
      "A yo-yo"
    ], 
    "question": "With what did cricketer Mansoor Ali Khan Pataudi frequently play with in his hands?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Southpaw", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Goofy", 
      "Regular", 
      "Orthodox"
    ], 
    "question": "What Do You Call A Boxer Who Leads With Their Right? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Andy Cole", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Wayne Rooney", 
      "Sergio Aguero"
    ], 
    "question": "Alan Shearer was the first player to score 200 Premiership goals. Who was the second?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Martina Navratilova", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steffi Graf", 
      "Chris Evert", 
      "Margaret Court", 
      "Billie Jean King"
    ], 
    "question": "Who was the 1978 Wimbledon Women's Singles champ?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Silverstone", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Brands Hatch", 
      "Thruxton", 
      "Knockhill"
    ], 
    "question": "At Which Course Is The British Grand Prix Held?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Two", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Five", 
      "Four", 
      "Three"
    ], 
    "question": "In a game of netball how many players on a team are allowed To score?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "110m Hurdles", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Pole Vault", 
      "Discus", 
      "Steeple Chase"
    ], 
    "question": "In Which Athletic Event Was Colin Jackson A Dominant Figure?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "David Beckham", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Michael Owen", 
      "Wayne Rooney", 
      "David Seaman"
    ], 
    "question": "Which English Footballer Was Sent Off In The 1998 World Cup?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Evander Holyfield", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Mike Tyson", 
      "Oscar De La Hoya", 
      "Floyd Mayweather"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Heavweight Boxer Was Known As The Real Deal?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Greece", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Argentina", 
      "Japan", 
      "Australia", 
      "Russia"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Country Hosted The 2004 Summer Olympics?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Ice Hockey", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "American Football", 
      "Basketball", 
      "Tennis", 
      "Swimming"
    ], 
    "question": "In which sport is the Canadian Wayne Gretzky an all time great?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Sporting Lisbon", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Porto", 
      "Real Madrid", 
      "Benfica"
    ], 
    "question": "Prior To Joining Manchester Utd In 2007 Which Club Did Cristiano Ronaldo Play For?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Five", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Six", 
      "Seven", 
      "Eight"
    ], 
    "question": "How Many Players Are In A Basketball Team?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "3,000 Metres", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "10,000 Metres", 
      "5,000 Metres", 
      "8,000 Metres"
    ], 
    "question": "Over What Distance Is A Steeple Chase Run?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Shigeru Miyamoto", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Yu Suzuki", 
      "Satoru Iwata", 
      "Gunpei Yokoi"
    ], 
    "question": "Which legendary games designer/producer created the Super Mario Brothers franchise for Nintendo?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Golf", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Boxing", 
      "Tennis", 
      "Snooker"
    ], 
    "question": "In which sport does Lee Westwood play?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Barcelona", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Rome", 
      "London", 
      "Paris"
    ], 
    "question": "Where were the 1992 Olympics held?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "American Football", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Soccer", 
      "Baseball", 
      "Basketball"
    ], 
    "question": "What sport do the following terms belong to - \"Tight End & Wide Receiver\"?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Oche", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Div", 
      "The Par", 
      "The Sod"
    ], 
    "question": "What Is the Mark Behind Which Dart Player Must Stand Called?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Alan Shearer", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Wayne Rooney", 
      "Andy Cole", 
      "Gary Lineker"
    ], 
    "question": "Who Was The First Player To Score 100 Goals In The Football Premiership League?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "10", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "7", 
      "5", 
      "13"
    ], 
    "question": "How Many Cards Are You Dealt In A Game Of Gin Rummy? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Aberdeen", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Rangers", 
      "Celtic", 
      "Hearts"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Scottish Football Club Boasted The First All Seater Football Stadium In Britain?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Four", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Six", 
      "Three", 
      "Five"
    ], 
    "question": "How many human players are in a polo team?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Darts", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Snooker", 
      "Horse Racing", 
      "Bowling"
    ], 
    "question": "With which sport would you have associated Jocky Wilson?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Calcutta Cup", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Davis Cup", 
      "Roobis Cup", 
      "Hadrian's Cup"
    ], 
    "question": "Name The Rugby Union Trophy For Which England & Scotland Compete", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "110m Hurdles", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Pole Vault", 
      "Discus", 
      "Steeple Chase"
    ], 
    "question": "In Which Athletic Event Was Colin Jackson A Dominant Figure?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Leeds United", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Chelsea", 
      "Newcastle United", 
      "Everton"
    ], 
    "question": "A Statue Of Billy Bremner Stands Outside The Ground Of Which Football Ground?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Martina Navratilova", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steffi Graf", 
      "Chris Evert", 
      "Margaret Court", 
      "Billie Jean King"
    ], 
    "question": "Who was the 1978 Wimbledon Women's Singles champ?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Pong", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Space Invaders", 
      "Pacman", 
      "Tetris"
    ], 
    "question": "What arcade game became a hit in 1973?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Butterfly", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Dragonfly", 
      "Mayfly", 
      "Horsefly"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Swimming Stroke Was Introduced Into Competition In 1952", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Ipswich Town", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Plymouth Argyle", 
      "Norwich City", 
      "Bristol Rovers"
    ], 
    "question": "Which English football team are nicknamed the Tractor Boys?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Lord's", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Fenway Park", 
      "Camp Nou", 
      "Wrigley Field"
    ], 
    "question": "At which sporting venue are the Grace Gates?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "A Driver Has Been Disqualified", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Race Has Been Won", 
      "A Driver Has Died", 
      "The Fastest Lap Has Been Set"
    ], 
    "question": "In Formula One what does it mean when they are waving a black flag?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "100 Metres", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Javelin", 
      "Pole Vault", 
      "800 Metres"
    ], 
    "question": "In A Decathlon What Is The First Event", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Cockfighting", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Rugby", 
      "Horse Racing", 
      "Tennis"
    ], 
    "question": "In what sport did the word 'crestfallen' originate?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Croquet", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tennis", 
      "Badminton", 
      "Billiards"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Game Makes Use Of Hoops", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Swim Across The English Channel", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Fly Solo Across the Atlantic", 
      "Run a marathon in under 2.5 hours"
    ], 
    "question": "What in 1926, did Gertrude Ederle become the first woman to do?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "4", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "6", 
      "11", 
      "2"
    ], 
    "question": "How Many Players Are In A Polo Team?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "One", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Two", 
      "Three", 
      "Four"
    ], 
    "question": "How many referees work a soccer game?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "John McEnroe", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Pete Sampras", 
      "Bjorn Borg", 
      "Ivan Lendl"
    ], 
    "question": "Which tennis player was famous for the 'You cannot be serious'' outburst?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Golf", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tennis", 
      "Boxing", 
      "Rugby"
    ], 
    "question": "With Which Sport Would You Associate Colin Montgomerie?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Eric Bristow", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Gerwyn Price", 
      "Gary Anderson", 
      "Phil Taylor"
    ], 
    "question": "Which darts player became the first in his sport to receive an MBE in 1989?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Eleven", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Fourteen", 
      "Thirteen", 
      "Twelve"
    ], 
    "question": "How many players make up a field hockey team?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Formula One", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Rugby", 
      "Cricket", 
      "Tennis"
    ], 
    "question": "Monza & Silverstone Are Venues For Which Sport?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Lord's", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Fenway Park", 
      "Camp Nou", 
      "Wrigley Field"
    ], 
    "question": "At which sporting venue are the Grace Gates?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Face Off", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Drop Puck", 
      "Toss Up", 
      "Throw Down"
    ], 
    "question": "In hockey, what is the equivalent of a rugby scrum?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Barcelona", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Rome", 
      "London", 
      "Paris"
    ], 
    "question": "Where were the 1992 Olympics held?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "300", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "100", 
      "200", 
      "250"
    ], 
    "question": "In tenpin bowling, how many points does a perfect game consist of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Miami", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Dallas", 
      "Los Angeles", 
      "Atlanta"
    ], 
    "question": "In American Football, where is the Orange Bowl?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Andy Cole", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Wayne Rooney", 
      "Sergio Aguero"
    ], 
    "question": "Alan Shearer was the first player to score 200 Premiership goals. Who was the second?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Oxford", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Manchester", 
      "London", 
      "York", 
      "Southampton", 
      "Norwich"
    ], 
    "question": "In which English city did Roger Bannister become the first man to run a mile in under 4 minutes? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Face Off", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Drop Puck", 
      "Toss Up", 
      "Throw Down"
    ], 
    "question": "In hockey, what is the equivalent of a rugby scrum?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Swim Across The English Channel", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Fly Solo Across the Atlantic", 
      "Run a marathon in under 2.5 hours"
    ], 
    "question": "What in 1926, did Gertrude Ederle become the first woman to do?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Sailboat racing", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Baseball", 
      "Volleyball", 
      "Golf"
    ], 
    "question": "In which sport is the America's Cup awarded? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Butterfly", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Dragonfly", 
      "Mayfly", 
      "Horsefly"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Swimming Stroke Was Introduced Into Competition In 1952", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Basketball", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Volleyball", 
      "Football", 
      "Baseball"
    ], 
    "question": "What Sport Do The Harlem Globetrotters Play?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Golden Bear", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Black Tiger", 
      "Silver Swan", 
      "Red Eagle"
    ], 
    "question": "What was Jack Nicklaus' nickname?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "A glass eye", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "A deck of cards", 
      "Keys", 
      "A yo-yo"
    ], 
    "question": "With what did cricketer Mansoor Ali Khan Pataudi frequently play with in his hands?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Andy Cole", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Wayne Rooney", 
      "Sergio Aguero"
    ], 
    "question": "Alan Shearer was the first player to score 200 Premiership goals. Who was the second?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "4", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "6", 
      "11", 
      "2"
    ], 
    "question": "How Many Players Are In A Polo Team?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Long Jump", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "High Jump", 
      "Triple Jump", 
      "Pole Vault"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Jump Event Did Carl Lewis Specialize In As Well As The Sprint?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Saints", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Gators", 
      "Rockets", 
      "Brass"
    ], 
    "question": "American Football: The New Orleans __________.", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Saints", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Gators", 
      "Rockets", 
      "Brass"
    ], 
    "question": "American Football: The New Orleans __________.", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "American Football", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Soccer", 
      "Baseball", 
      "Basketball"
    ], 
    "question": "What sport do the following terms belong to - \"Tight End & Wide Receiver\"?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "4", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "6", 
      "8", 
      "10"
    ], 
    "question": "How Many Tournaments make up a Grand Slam In Golf? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Four", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Six", 
      "Three", 
      "Five"
    ], 
    "question": "How many seams are there on a football (American)?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Ivory Coast", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Nigeria", 
      "Cameroon", 
      "Senegal"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Country Did Chelsea Striker Didier Drogba Represent At International Level?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Alan Shearer", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Wayne Rooney", 
      "Andy Cole", 
      "Gary Lineker"
    ], 
    "question": "Who Was The First Player To Score 100 Goals In The Football Premiership League?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "David Ginola", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Alan Shearer", 
      "David Beckham", 
      "Matt Le Tissier"
    ], 
    "question": "In 1999, which Premier League footballer was voted PFA player of the year?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Five", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Twelve", 
      "Two", 
      "Nine"
    ], 
    "question": "How Many Consecutive Wimbledon Titles Did Bjorn Borg Win?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Everton", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Chelsea", 
      "Liverpool", 
      "Sunderland"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Football Team Are Known As The Toffees", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Baby Pac-Man", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Miss Pac-Man", 
      "Mrs Pac-Man", 
      "Super Pac-Man"
    ], 
    "question": "What was the hybrid pinball/video game in the Pac-Man series?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Newcastle United", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Liverpool", 
      "Arsenal", 
      "Aston Villa"
    ], 
    "question": "In 1992 Kevin Keegan became manager of which football club?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Sailboat racing", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Baseball", 
      "Volleyball", 
      "Golf"
    ], 
    "question": "In which sport is the America's Cup awarded? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Argentina", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South Africa", 
      "Uruguay", 
      "Brazil"
    ], 
    "question": "The Pumas Are The Rugby Team Of Which Country?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Jack", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Mike", 
      "Chuck", 
      "Rob"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Boys Name Is Also The Name Of The Object Ball In Bowls?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "A Spare", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "A Strike", 
      "A Near", 
      "A Close"
    ], 
    "question": "In Bowling What Is The Term For Knocking Down All Ten Pins With 2 Consecutive Balls?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Italy", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Spain", 
      "Germany", 
      "England"
    ], 
    "question": "Who Did France Beat To Win The Euro 2000 Football Final?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Mrs White, Miss Scarlet, Mrs Peacock", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Mrs Plum, Miss Jade, Mrs Scarlett", 
      "Mrs White, Miss Gold, Mrs Green", 
      "Miss Silver, Mrs Pink, Mrs Indigo"
    ], 
    "question": "Name The 3 Female Characters In The Game Cluedo", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Nintendo Entertainment System", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Natural Emitting Screen", 
      "Near Energy Source"
    ], 
    "question": "What does the acronym \"NES\" stand for?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Face Off", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Drop Puck", 
      "Toss Up", 
      "Throw Down"
    ], 
    "question": "In hockey, what is the equivalent of a rugby scrum?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Andy Cole", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Wayne Rooney", 
      "Sergio Aguero"
    ], 
    "question": "Alan Shearer was the first player to score 200 Premiership goals. Who was the second?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Shigeru Miyamoto", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Yu Suzuki", 
      "Satoru Iwata", 
      "Gunpei Yokoi"
    ], 
    "question": "Which legendary games designer/producer created the Super Mario Brothers franchise for Nintendo?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Golf", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Boxing", 
      "Tennis", 
      "Snooker"
    ], 
    "question": "In which sport does Lee Westwood play?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "3,000 Metres", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "10,000 Metres", 
      "5,000 Metres", 
      "8,000 Metres"
    ], 
    "question": "Over What Distance Is A Steeple Chase Run?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Catcher", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Pitcher", 
      "Guard", 
      "Steer"
    ], 
    "question": "What Is The Name Of The Player In Baseball Who Is Positioned Behind The Home Plate", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Let", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Dus", 
      "Par", 
      "See"
    ], 
    "question": "What 3 Letter Word It The Name Given To A Replayed Point In Tennis?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Everton", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Chelsea", 
      "Liverpool", 
      "Sunderland"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Football Team Are Known As The Toffees", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Viv Anderson", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Raheem Sterling", 
      "John Barnes", 
      "Paul Ince"
    ], 
    "question": "Which footballer was England's first black player?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "100 Metres", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Javelin", 
      "Pole Vault", 
      "800 Metres"
    ], 
    "question": "In A Decathlon What Is The First Event", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "A glass eye", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "A deck of cards", 
      "Keys", 
      "A yo-yo"
    ], 
    "question": "With what did cricketer Mansoor Ali Khan Pataudi frequently play with in his hands?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Golden Bear", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Black Tiger", 
      "Silver Swan", 
      "Red Eagle"
    ], 
    "question": "What was Jack Nicklaus' nickname?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "A glass eye", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "A deck of cards", 
      "Keys", 
      "A yo-yo"
    ], 
    "question": "With what did cricketer Mansoor Ali Khan Pataudi frequently play with in his hands?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Yorkshire", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Lancashire", 
      "Staffordshire", 
      "Middlesex"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Team Has Won The County Cricket Championships The Most Often?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Five", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Twelve", 
      "Two", 
      "Nine"
    ], 
    "question": "How Many Consecutive Wimbledon Titles Did Bjorn Borg Win?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "4", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "6", 
      "11", 
      "2"
    ], 
    "question": "How Many Players Are In A Polo Team?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "A Driver Has Been Disqualified", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Race Has Been Won", 
      "A Driver Has Died", 
      "The Fastest Lap Has Been Set"
    ], 
    "question": "In Formula One what does it mean when they are waving a black flag?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Barcelona", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Rome", 
      "London", 
      "Paris"
    ], 
    "question": "Where were the 1992 Olympics held?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Mrs White, Miss Scarlet, Mrs Peacock", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Mrs Plum, Miss Jade, Mrs Scarlett", 
      "Mrs White, Miss Gold, Mrs Green", 
      "Miss Silver, Mrs Pink, Mrs Indigo"
    ], 
    "question": "Name The 3 Female Characters In The Game Cluedo", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Grouse", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Deer", 
      "Fox", 
      "Pheasant"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Shooting Season Begins On The Glorious Twelfth?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Steffi Graff", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Billie Jean King", 
      "Venus Williams", 
      "Maria Sharapova"
    ], 
    "question": "Which player won her last tennis Grand Slam Tournament in Paris in 1999?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Four", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Two", 
      "One", 
      "Six"
    ], 
    "question": "How many seams are there on an American football?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Five", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Twelve", 
      "Two", 
      "Nine"
    ], 
    "question": "How Many Consecutive Wimbledon Titles Did Bjorn Borg Win?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Four", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Six", 
      "Three", 
      "Five"
    ], 
    "question": "How many seams are there on a football (American)?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Two", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Five", 
      "Four", 
      "Three"
    ], 
    "question": "In a game of netball how many players on a team are allowed To score?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Andre Agassi", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Roger Federer", 
      "Pete Sampras", 
      "Andy Roddick"
    ], 
    "question": "In April 2003 Who Became The Oldest Man To Be Rated No1 In The World Tennis Association Rankings At The Age Of 33?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Hill", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Schumacher", 
      "Hunt", 
      "Villeneuve"
    ], 
    "question": "What Surname Has Been Shared By Three Formula One Champions Of The 20th Century?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "American Football", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Soccer", 
      "Baseball", 
      "Basketball"
    ], 
    "question": "What sport do the following terms belong to - \"Tight End & Wide Receiver\"?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Trampoline", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Golf", 
      "Wrestling", 
      "Squash"
    ], 
    "question": "What sport was first introduced into the Olympics in 2000?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Andy Cole", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Wayne Rooney", 
      "Sergio Aguero"
    ], 
    "question": "Alan Shearer was the first player to score 200 Premiership goals. Who was the second?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Let", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Dus", 
      "Par", 
      "See"
    ], 
    "question": "What 3 Letter Word It The Name Given To A Replayed Point In Tennis?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Calcutta Cup", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Davis Cup", 
      "Roobis Cup", 
      "Hadrian's Cup"
    ], 
    "question": "Name The Rugby Union Trophy For Which England & Scotland Compete", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Viv Anderson", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Raheem Sterling", 
      "John Barnes", 
      "Paul Ince"
    ], 
    "question": "Which footballer was England's first black player?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "An Ice Skating Rink", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "A Football Pitch", 
      "A Tennis Court", 
      "A Rugby Pitch"
    ], 
    "question": "In the world of sport what has the maximum dimensions of 60 metres by 30 metres?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "300", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "100", 
      "200", 
      "250"
    ], 
    "question": "In tenpin bowling, how many points does a perfect game consist of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "One", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Two", 
      "Three", 
      "Four"
    ], 
    "question": "How many referees work a soccer game?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Uruguay", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Brazil", 
      "West Germany", 
      "France"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Country Won The First Football World Cup? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Surfing", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Skate Boarding", 
      "Skiing", 
      "Boxing"
    ], 
    "question": "What sport do the following terms belong to - \"Hotdog & Bottom Trun\"?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Basketball", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Volleyball", 
      "Football", 
      "Baseball"
    ], 
    "question": "What Sport Do The Harlem Globetrotters Play?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Darts", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Snooker", 
      "Horse Racing", 
      "Bowling"
    ], 
    "question": "With which sport would you have associated Jocky Wilson?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Black", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "White", 
      "Red", 
      "Brown"
    ], 
    "question": "What Colour Is The 8 Ball In A Game Of Pool?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Two", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Five", 
      "Four", 
      "Three"
    ], 
    "question": "In a game of netball how many players on a team are allowed To score?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "300", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "100", 
      "200", 
      "250"
    ], 
    "question": "In tenpin bowling, how many points does a perfect game consist of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Italy", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Spain", 
      "Germany", 
      "England"
    ], 
    "question": "Who Did France Beat To Win The Euro 2000 Football Final?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Black", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "White", 
      "Red", 
      "Brown"
    ], 
    "question": "What Colour Is The 8 Ball In A Game Of Pool?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Golf", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tennis", 
      "Boxing", 
      "Rugby"
    ], 
    "question": "With Which Sport Would You Associate Colin Montgomerie?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Golf", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Boxing", 
      "Tennis", 
      "Snooker"
    ], 
    "question": "In which sport does Lee Westwood play?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Super Mario Bros.", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Zelda", 
      "Call of Duty", 
      "Halo"
    ], 
    "question": "If you're killing a goomba, what game are you playing?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Golden Bear", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Black Tiger", 
      "Silver Swan", 
      "Red Eagle"
    ], 
    "question": "What was Jack Nicklaus' nickname?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Argentina", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South Africa", 
      "Uruguay", 
      "Brazil"
    ], 
    "question": "The Pumas Are The Rugby Team Of Which Country?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Uruguay", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Brazil", 
      "West Germany", 
      "France"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Country Won The First Football World Cup? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Miami", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Dallas", 
      "Los Angeles", 
      "Atlanta"
    ], 
    "question": "In American Football, where is the Orange Bowl?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "An Ice Skating Rink", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "A Football Pitch", 
      "A Tennis Court", 
      "A Rugby Pitch"
    ], 
    "question": "In the world of sport what has the maximum dimensions of 60 metres by 30 metres?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Table Tennis", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Pool", 
      "Volleyball", 
      "Wrestling"
    ], 
    "question": "In Which Sport Was Desmond Douglas Britain's Leading Competitor?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Sport and Leisure", 
    "correctAnswer": "Alan Shearer", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Wayne Rooney", 
      "Andy Cole", 
      "Gary Lineker"
    ], 
    "question": "Who Was The First Player To Score 100 Goals In The Football Premiership League?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }
]
